const topFiveTopics = {
    'empty': [
        {prompt: "Select a category"}
    ],
    'music': [
        {prompt: "90s rappers", popAnswer: ['B.I.G.', '2PAC', 'Nas', 'Jayz', 'DMX'], rank: 0},
        {prompt: "Early 2000s alt rock bands", popAnswer: ['Third Eye Blind', 'Eve 6', 'Foo Fighters', 'Red Hot Chili Peppers', 'Blind Melon'], rank: 0},
        {prompt: "Artists all time", popAnswer: ['Michael Jackson', 'Prince', 'Stevie Wonder', 'Bill Withers', 'Bob Dylan'], rank: 0},
        {prompt: "Solo artists all time", popAnswer: ['dummy data', 'dummy data', 'dummy data', 'dummy data', 'dummy data'], rank: 0}
    ],
    'sports': [
        {prompt: "Football teams all time", popAnswer: ['Browns', 'Steelers', 'Packers', '49ers', 'Pats'], rank: 0},
        {prompt: "Basketball teams all time", popAnswer: ['Nuggets', 'GSW', 'Heat', 'Magic', 'Lakers'], rank: 0}
    ],
    'food': [
        {prompt: "Crunchy snack foods", popAnswer: ['Lays chips', 'Takis', "Snyder's pretzels", 'Kettle corn', 'Lucky charms'], rank: 0},
        {prompt: "Candy", popAnswer: ['Skittles', 'M&Ms', 'Twix', 'Good & Plentys', 'Snickers'], rank: 0}
    ],
    'movies': [
        {prompt: "Horror movie all time", popAnswer: ['The Shining', 'Nightmare on Elm Street', 'Hereditary', 'Midsommer', 'Scream'], rank: 0},
        {prompt: "Comedy movie all time", popAnswer: ['dummy data', 'dummy data', 'dummy data', 'dummy data', 'dummy data'], rank: 0}
    ]
}

export default topFiveTopics

